<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-01-17T23:10:28+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Minamisawa Senri</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Prologue - the Day of the Beginning</title><link href="/2018/12/04/1543965666.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - Prologue - the Day of the Beginning" /><published>2018-12-04T23:21:06+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-04T23:21:06+00:00</updated><id>/2018/12/04/1543965666</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/12/04/1543965666.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - Prologue - the Day of the Beginning
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1543965666.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  This short Drama was released with the original Xbox One opening/ending single CD.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The prologue explores some of the early days of the Newspaper Club, although at moments it turns bittersweet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  My thanks go out to Mouse (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/5zzb&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@5zzb&lt;/a&gt;) for giving me a Japanese transcript to work from.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Prologue - the Day of the Beginning This short Drama was released with the original Xbox One opening/ending single CD. The prologue explores some of the early days of the Newspaper Club, although at moments it turns bittersweet. My thanks go out to Mouse (@5zzb) for giving me a Japanese transcript to work from. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Far too late - slumbering Fools</title><link href="/2018/11/26/1543268900.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - Far too late - slumbering Fools" /><published>2018-11-26T21:48:20+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T21:48:20+00:00</updated><id>/2018/11/26/1543268900</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/26/1543268900.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - Far too late - slumbering Fools
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1543268900.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  This is the big one. This Drama CD was part of the Playstation limited edition release.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The main character of this story is Mio. We travel into her past, to investigate the reason as to why she harbours a deep hatred for all Gigalomaniacs.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    Major spoilers for the ending of Chaos;Child lie inside, along with minor Steins;Gate spoilers.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Far too late - slumbering Fools This is the big one. This Drama CD was part of the Playstation limited edition release. The main character of this story is Mio. We travel into her past, to investigate the reason as to why she harbours a deep hatred for all Gigalomaniacs. Major spoilers for the ending of Chaos;Child lie inside, along with minor Steins;Gate spoilers. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Investigating the mysterious ‘Seven Wonders of Shibuya’</title><link href="/2018/10/27/1540676700.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - Investigating the mysterious 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya'" /><published>2018-10-27T21:45:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-27T21:45:00+00:00</updated><id>/2018/10/27/1540676700</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/27/1540676700.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - Investigating the mysterious 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya'
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1540676700.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Time for the second Drama CD from the DVD/BD releases.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  This focuses on Hinae - at the weekend, Hinae 'persuades' Taku to help her investigate the 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya', as research for a story.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Investigating the mysterious 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya' Time for the second Drama CD from the DVD/BD releases. This focuses on Hinae - at the weekend, Hinae 'persuades' Taku to help her investigate the 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya', as research for a story. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - The Right-sider and a certain day off</title><link href="/2018/10/01/1538423180.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - The Right-sider and a certain day off" /><published>2018-10-01T19:46:20+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-01T19:46:20+00:00</updated><id>/2018/10/01/1538423180</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/01/1538423180.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - The Right-sider and a certain day off
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1538423180.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Onto the first of the Drama CDs from the DVD/BD releases.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The story for today focuses on Nono - whilst out shopping with Nono and Yui, Takuru's powerful delusions take hold once more.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Note, I am using the artwork which corresponds to the character featured in the Drama CD, not the artwork that appeared with the Drama CD.
  They wanted main girl on the first release so everything got shifted back one.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - The Right-sider and a certain day off Onto the first of the Drama CDs from the DVD/BD releases. The story for today focuses on Nono - whilst out shopping with Nono and Yui, Takuru's powerful delusions take hold once more. Note, I am using the artwork which corresponds to the character featured in the Drama CD, not the artwork that appeared with the Drama CD. They wanted main girl on the first release so everything got shifted back one. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - The narrow path off the beaten track</title><link href="/2018/09/23/1537729040.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - The narrow path off the beaten track" /><published>2018-09-23T18:57:20+00:00</published><updated>2018-09-23T18:57:20+00:00</updated><id>/2018/09/23/1537729040</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/09/23/1537729040.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - The narrow path off the beaten track
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Time to start up translating Chaos;Child content once more. Here for you today is the script of the Comiket 91 Drama CD.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The story revolves around the Newspaper Club trip to a traditional Japanese inn, complete with onsen. Various activities may or may not occur, depending on the delusion you desire.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  As I have limited video skills; for now it is just a script. I aim to try for one Drama CD each week, starting next on the BD/DVD bonuses.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - The narrow path off the beaten track Time to start up translating Chaos;Child content once more. Here for you today is the script of the Comiket 91 Drama CD. The story revolves around the Newspaper Club trip to a traditional Japanese inn, complete with onsen. Various activities may or may not occur, depending on the delusion you desire. As I have limited video skills; for now it is just a script. I aim to try for one Drama CD each week, starting next on the BD/DVD bonuses. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Minikui Mojika no Ko - overview and lyrics</title><link href="/2018/08/16/1534456000.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Minikui Mojika no Ko - overview and lyrics" /><published>2018-08-16T21:46:40+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-16T21:46:40+00:00</updated><id>/2018/08/16/1534456000</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/16/1534456000.html">&lt;h3&gt;
	Minikui Mojika no Ko - overview and lyrics
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Minikui Mojika no Ko focuses on making you and the characters suffer. It is devoid of any light scenes, the sex scenes are bitter and glimmers of hope are quickly snuffed out.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	A quick overview of the premise. The protagonist, Tanezaki Suteru, is the ugliest person in the world. Having gained a spot in one of the most prestigious schools in the country, he faces daily bullying from the rest of his class. However, he has a special ability/curse; when he gazes at the faces of others, he can read their hearts, with words materialising beside them - Mojika. After another bullied member of his class is forced to falsely confess their love for him, he decides to use his powers to escape and take revenge.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The majority of the game is spent with your gaze directed towards the ground; to objects lying on the floor and the feet of others. The art style focuses on realism and works well with the story themes. Choices are made through deciding when to look up and to use the power of the Mojika. The majority of the main routes are easy to navigate to, but the true route takes a bit more effort (fortunately, there are hints in the stub endings to guide you on your way).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	If you enjoy reading stories which abuse your feelings, make you uncomfortable and have harsh endings, look no further.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;cc&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%; max-height: 50vh; height: 100vh;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ms9MTSs438o?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	I have translated the lyrics to the opening and ending songs.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/?post=1534455999&quot;&gt;
		Opening - 憐 (Pitiful)
	&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/?post=1534455888&quot;&gt;
		Ending - 空 (Sky)
	&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	- Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Minikui Mojika no Ko - overview and lyrics Minikui Mojika no Ko focuses on making you and the characters suffer. It is devoid of any light scenes, the sex scenes are bitter and glimmers of hope are quickly snuffed out. A quick overview of the premise. The protagonist, Tanezaki Suteru, is the ugliest person in the world. Having gained a spot in one of the most prestigious schools in the country, he faces daily bullying from the rest of his class. However, he has a special ability/curse; when he gazes at the faces of others, he can read their hearts, with words materialising beside them - Mojika. After another bullied member of his class is forced to falsely confess their love for him, he decides to use his powers to escape and take revenge. The majority of the game is spent with your gaze directed towards the ground; to objects lying on the floor and the feet of others. The art style focuses on realism and works well with the story themes. Choices are made through deciding when to look up and to use the power of the Mojika. The majority of the main routes are easy to navigate to, but the true route takes a bit more effort (fortunately, there are hints in the stub endings to guide you on your way). If you enjoy reading stories which abuse your feelings, make you uncomfortable and have harsh endings, look no further. I have translated the lyrics to the opening and ending songs. Opening - 憐 (Pitiful) Ending - 空 (Sky) - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">憐 (Pitiful) lyrics</title><link href="/2018/08/16/1534455999.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="憐 (Pitiful) lyrics" /><published>2018-08-16T21:46:39+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-16T21:46:39+00:00</updated><id>/2018/08/16/1534455999</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/16/1534455999.html">&lt;h3&gt;
	憐 (Pitiful) lyrics
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1534455999.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The opening song for Minikui Mojika no Ko. Note: in part, it seems to reference a poem; &quot;Du bist wie eine Blume&quot;. If you were not sure how much suffering is involved in the story, this may help clarify.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Kanji Ver. - 憐&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
ああ　絶望さえ
ああ　甘く響いた
瓦礫さえも　花のようだ
ただ悲しく

ああ　傷跡まで
ああ　甘い想い出
完璧まで　遥か遠く
ただ悲しく

美しい声　聴こえめても
残酷に痛みだけ刺さる
醜い声　視えたとして
ただ悲しく

ああ　壊れる音
ああ　甘い調べ
望んだ時　夢見ている
ただ悲しく

消えない意識　振りほどいて
とりとめに虚しさだけ抱いて
刹那の景色　頬撫でた
ただ悲しく

美しい声　聴こえめても
残酷に痛みだけ刺さる
醜い声　視えたとして
ただ悲しく

可憐
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Romaji Ver. - aware&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
aa, zetsubou sae
aa, amaku hibiita
gareki sae mo, hana no you da
tada kanashiku

aa, kizuato made
aa, amai omoide
kanpeki made haruka tooku
tada kanashiku

utsukushii koe kikoemete mo
zankoku ni itami dake sasaru
minikui koe mieta toshite
tada kanashiku

aa, kowareru oto
aa, amai shirabe
nozonda toki yume miteiru
tada kanashiku

kienai ishiki furi hodoite
toritomeni munashisa dake daite
setsuna no keshiki hoho nadeta
tada kanashiku

utsukushii koe kikoemete mo
zankoku ni itami dake sasaru
minikui koe mieta toshite
tada kanashiku

karen
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;English Ver. - Pitiful&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
Ah, even the depths of despair
Ah, the sweet reverberations
Even the rubble invokes the same feeling as the flowers
'tis merely sadness

Ah, until scars remain
Ah, the sweet memories
Until perfection is reached; so distant, so far
'tis merely sadness

Even though I can hear your beautiful voice
I am cruelly stricken with suffering
As I can gaze at your ugly voice
'tis merely sadness

Ah, the sounds of breaking
Ah, the sweet observations
The times I longed for can only be seen within my dreams
'tis merely sadness

Relinquish me from this unwavering awareness
Let me embrace only meaningless nothingness
This ephemeral scenery; as you caress my face
'tis merely sadness

Even though I can hear your beautiful voice
I am cruelly stricken with suffering
As I can gaze at your ugly voice
'tis merely sadness

How pitiful
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	- Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">憐 (Pitiful) lyrics The opening song for Minikui Mojika no Ko. Note: in part, it seems to reference a poem; &quot;Du bist wie eine Blume&quot;. If you were not sure how much suffering is involved in the story, this may help clarify. Kanji Ver. - 憐 ああ　絶望さえ ああ　甘く響いた 瓦礫さえも　花のようだ ただ悲しく</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">空 (Sky) lyrics</title><link href="/2018/08/16/1534455888.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="空 (Sky) lyrics" /><published>2018-08-16T21:44:48+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-16T21:44:48+00:00</updated><id>/2018/08/16/1534455888</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/16/1534455888.html">&lt;h3&gt;
	空 (Sky) lyrics
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1534455888.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The ending song for Minikui Mojika no Ko. A tad spoilery, if you read between the lines. Or the Mojika.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Kanji Ver. - 空&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
冷たい空　見上げている
ねぇ　ねぇ 　ねぇ
冷たい風　美しくて
ねぇ　ねぇ 　ねぇ

あなたの嘘　ホントになれば
わたしの罪　溶け消えるかな？
繋いだ手の温もりだけが
ねぇ　ねぇ 　ねぇ

終わりなんてあっけないね
ねぇ　ねぇ 　ねぇ

わたしの嘘　ホントになれば
あなたの罪　溶け消えるかな？
繋いだ手の温もりだけが
ねぇ　ねぇ 　ねぇ

ふたりの星　輪廻の如く
ふたりの雪　記憶の彼方
新しい命　足跡になれ
ねぇ　ねぇ 　ねぇ
ねぇ　ねぇ
ねぇ
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Romaji Ver. - sora&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
tsumetai sora miagete iru
ne ne ne
tsumetai kaze utsukushikute
ne ne ne

anata no uso honto ni nareba
watashi no tsumi tokekieru kana?
tsunaida te no nukumori dake ga
ne ne ne

owari nante akkenai ne
ne ne ne

watashi no uso honto ni nareba
anata no tsumi tokekieru kana?
tsunaida te no nukumori dake ga
ne ne ne

futari no hoshi rinne no gotoku
futari no yuki kioku no kanata
atarashii inochi ashiatto ni nare
ne ne ne
ne ne
ne
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;English Ver. - Sky&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
Gazing up into the cold sky
Oh, oh, oh
The cold wind, in all its beauty
Oh, oh, oh

If your lies were to become reality
Would my sins be swept away?
To leave only the warmth in our intertwined hands
Oh, oh, oh

The end cannot claim us here
Oh, oh, oh

If my lies were to become reality
Would your sins be swept away?
To leave only the warmth in our intertwined hands
Oh, oh, oh

Our stars, within the cycle of rebirth
Our snow, the depths of our memories
Unto the new life, becoming the footprint we leave behind
Oh, oh, oh
Oh, oh
Oh
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	- Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">空 (Sky) lyrics The ending song for Minikui Mojika no Ko. A tad spoilery, if you read between the lines. Or the Mojika. Kanji Ver. - 空 冷たい空　見上げている ねぇ　ねぇ 　ねぇ 冷たい風　美しくて ねぇ　ねぇ 　ねぇ</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child - Fake Sky End</title><link href="/2018/06/30/1530398689.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child - Fake Sky End" /><published>2018-06-30T22:44:49+00:00</published><updated>2018-06-30T22:44:49+00:00</updated><id>/2018/06/30/1530398689</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/06/30/1530398689.html">&lt;h3&gt;
	Chaos;Child - Fake Sky End
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;cc&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%; max-height: 50vh; height: 100vh;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/E4_QJnUb_bI?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	In the final release of Chaos;Child, Nono did not have a bad ending route.
	Said bad ending was cut from the final game but the files still exist in a broken state (the script crashes if you run it, sound effects are missing and so on).
	The bad end splits after Senri reveals her true form and Serika dies.
	Having returned to school, Senri decides to visit the grave of Nono; this time without inviting Takuru.
	After visiting the grave and receiving ghostly encouragement, Senri turns to head home…
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
	dl da {
		float: left;
		text-align: left;
		width: 25%;
		font-weight: bold;
	}
	dl ds {
		float: left;
		text-align: left;
		width: 75%;
	}
	dl dn {
		float: left;
		text-align: left;
		margin-left: 25%;
		width: 75%;
	}
	dl br {
		width: 100%;
		display: block;
		margin-top: 1em;
		margin-bottom: 1em;
	}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;dl&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;I felt the presence of someone, standing behind me.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Mmn?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;As I turned around to see their face, they too moved.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Huh?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;I feel a stabbing heat in my belly.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Ugh…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;I could not grasp what had happened.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;As I jaggedly lowered my gaze downwards, for some reason there was something piercing my clothes and stomach, covered in red.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Such an abnormal scene.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;This is…?&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Why did…?&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;From the end of a handle, crimson stains spread across my uniform.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Kawahara&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;It’s your…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Kawahara...?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Kawahara&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Everything… is your fault.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Kawahara stands before me.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;With both trembling hands extended out to the handle, he watches.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Kawahara&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Minamisawa. It’s all your fault.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Why?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Kawahara&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Kurusu has disappeared. You, who should be dead, suddenly showed up.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Kawahara stared off past me, chanting to himself.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Kawahara&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Strange, is it not?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Kawahara…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Kawahara&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;It’s you. It’s all your fault. It’s all your fault Kurusu has disappeared…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Kawahara&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Where are you? Give her back! Give me back my Nono…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;As the puddle at my feet swells ever larger, I feel the heat of my body flow out alongside.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;As if a gust of wind had blown straight through the hole to cool me down.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Kawahara&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Give her back… Nono… Give me back my Nono!&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Kawahara collapsed where he stood, gazing off into the distance whilst murmuring onwards to himself.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;I…&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Ugh…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;I raised my foot, as heavy as lead, and took a step forward.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Forwards.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;I have to… get back.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Forwards.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;I have to get back…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Forwards.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Takuru made us all tea... He is waiting for me…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Unable to stem the blood leaking from the wound, I feel my limbs grow colder still.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Even so, I…&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;I will get home.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Because.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Back to them…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;They are waiting for me.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Everyone is waiting… for me…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Strange…&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;The blue sky of minutes before had been engulfed in clouds.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;At some point, the colour had drained from this world, turning it white and black.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Even so.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Another step forwards.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Forwards.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Forwards…&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Senri&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;I have to… get… home…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;dl&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Yuto&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Sis still hasn’t come home.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Uki&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;I wonder what happened.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Takuru&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;She’s just a bit slow is all. She’s probably heading back now.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;The thread of murders linked to us are all over now.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;Unlike before, we have nothing dangerous left to be worried about.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Yuto&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Hey, I’m really hungry.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Uki&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Not yet. We have to wait for Senri.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Yuto&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;OK.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;Having said that…&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Takuru&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Senri sure is late.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;I had even gone out to buy her favourite cake especially for her.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Uki&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Huh?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Takuru&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;What’s up?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Uki&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;A siren?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Yuto&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;An ambulance? Or is it the police?&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Uki&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;I’m not sure… I wonder if something happened.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;da&gt;Takuru&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Either-or, doesn’t change anything.&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;dn&gt;I look up at the clock.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;dn&gt;It’s already 8.&lt;/dn&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

	&lt;da&gt;Takuru&lt;/da&gt;&lt;ds&gt;Senri… She sure is late…&lt;/ds&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/dl&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Senri did not deserve to die again.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	- Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child - Fake Sky End In the final release of Chaos;Child, Nono did not have a bad ending route. Said bad ending was cut from the final game but the files still exist in a broken state (the script crashes if you run it, sound effects are missing and so on). The bad end splits after Senri reveals her true form and Serika dies. Having returned to school, Senri decides to visit the grave of Nono; this time without inviting Takuru. After visiting the grave and receiving ghostly encouragement, Senri turns to head home… I felt the presence of someone, standing behind me.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Minamisawa Senri birthday giveaway</title><link href="/2018/06/06/1528319455.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Minamisawa Senri birthday giveaway" /><published>2018-06-06T21:10:55+00:00</published><updated>2018-06-06T21:10:55+00:00</updated><id>/2018/06/06/1528319455</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/06/06/1528319455.html">&lt;h3&gt;
	Minamisawa Senri birthday giveaway
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1528319455.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	To celebrate my birthday, I am giving away some duplicate Steam keys again. This year the available Steam keys are:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;eden*&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fault milestone one&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fault milestone two side:above&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Hatoful Boyfriend&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Highway Blossoms&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Higurashi When They Cry Hou - Ch.1 Onikakushi&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;HuniePop&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;If My Heart Had Wings&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;KARAKARA&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Loren The Amazon Princess - Deluxe Edition&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Root Double -Before Crime * After Days- Xtend Edition&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;RPG Maker VX Ace&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sakura Spirit&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sunrider Academy&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sunrider: Liberation Day - Captain's Edition&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;TyranoBuilder Visual Novel Studio&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Escape clauses:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Priority will be granted to Twitter followers who had followed me before the giveaway start (07:00 GMT 7th June). New followers will then be fed the leftovers.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;All entries should be made before 12:00 GMT 10th June; I will try to match up keys to entrants at this point and will contact winners afterwards with the result.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;If the game keys do not work then I will not be able to offer an alternative key. As far as I know, they should all be valid keys.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;I can rig this giveaway as much as I like - I may give some entrants their first choice or otherwise resort to randomisation or optimum pairings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	How to enter:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Send me a direct message on Twitter or mention me in a reply. State your desired game, or give a list in preference order in the case that your top priority choice is taken.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/sticker30.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	- Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Minamisawa Senri birthday giveaway To celebrate my birthday, I am giving away some duplicate Steam keys again. This year the available Steam keys are: eden* Fault milestone one Fault milestone two side:above Hatoful Boyfriend Highway Blossoms Higurashi When They Cry Hou - Ch.1 Onikakushi HuniePop If My Heart Had Wings KARAKARA Loren The Amazon Princess - Deluxe Edition Root Double -Before Crime * After Days- Xtend Edition RPG Maker VX Ace Sakura Spirit Sunrider Academy Sunrider: Liberation Day - Captain's Edition TyranoBuilder Visual Novel Studio Escape clauses: Priority will be granted to Twitter followers who had followed me before the giveaway start (07:00 GMT 7th June). New followers will then be fed the leftovers. All entries should be made before 12:00 GMT 10th June; I will try to match up keys to entrants at this point and will contact winners afterwards with the result. If the game keys do not work then I will not be able to offer an alternative key. As far as I know, they should all be valid keys. I can rig this giveaway as much as I like - I may give some entrants their first choice or otherwise resort to randomisation or optimum pairings. How to enter: Send me a direct message on Twitter or mention me in a reply. State your desired game, or give a list in preference order in the case that your top priority choice is taken. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry></feed>