<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-04-19T14:13:38+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Minamisawa Senri</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Love Chu Chu Drama CD - Kurusu Nono Monologue - The Sleep-Inducing Tune of Peace</title><link href="/2020/04/19/1587301025.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Love Chu Chu Drama CD - Kurusu Nono Monologue - The Sleep-Inducing Tune of Peace" /><published>2020-04-19T14:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-04-19T14:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2020/04/19/1587301025</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/04/19/1587301025.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Love Chu Chu Drama CD - Kurusu Nono Monologue - The Sleep-Inducing Tune of Peace
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1587301025.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  For Nono's birthday, here is a short Drama CD from the Love Chu Chu ending single CD.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Nono looks after Takuru whilst he is unwell. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Love Chu Chu Drama CD - Kurusu Nono Monologue - The Sleep-Inducing Tune of Peace For Nono's birthday, here is a short Drama CD from the Love Chu Chu ending single CD. Nono looks after Takuru whilst he is unwell. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Wish</title><link href="/2019/10/14/1571054400.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - Wish" /><published>2019-10-14T12:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-14T12:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2019/10/14/1571054400</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/10/14/1571054400.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - Wish
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1571054400.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Skipping to a slightly more serious Drama CD, the sixth from the DVD/BD releases.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  This one revolves around Serika. Triggered by a conversation with Sakuma, Serika wonders about her true desires - a wish of her own.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    Major spoilers for Chaos;Child. I advise not reading until after completing the true route. There are some slight hints to Fools as well, so you may wish to read that first.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Wish Skipping to a slightly more serious Drama CD, the sixth from the DVD/BD releases. This one revolves around Serika. Triggered by a conversation with Sakuma, Serika wonders about her true desires - a wish of her own. Major spoilers for Chaos;Child. I advise not reading until after completing the true route. There are some slight hints to Fools as well, so you may wish to read that first. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Robotics;Notes DaSH Summary Document</title><link href="/2019/07/04/1562278866.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Robotics;Notes DaSH Summary Document" /><published>2019-07-04T23:21:06+00:00</published><updated>2019-07-04T23:21:06+00:00</updated><id>/2019/07/04/1562278866</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/07/04/1562278866.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Robotics;Notes DaSH Summary Document
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1556658054.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The summary document includes the plot summary of all routes in Robotics;Notes DaSH, along with a route walkthrough.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Robotics;Notes DaSH continues on half a year after the events of Robotics;Notes. Having spent the previous months studying on the mainland, Kai returns to Tanegashima. On the same ferry rides a certain Super Hacker...
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  DaSH details the adventures of Daru and the returning Robotics;Notes cast. For the most part, the game is a fandisk and does not take itself too seriously. If you wish to skip such service, the reading order for the true route is provided.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/1DQBiLKmdfA3fXFb1nVegFbU8X9fqjupK2v6Ak9SjwiY/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the document here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Robotics;Notes DaSH Summary Document The summary document includes the plot summary of all routes in Robotics;Notes DaSH, along with a route walkthrough. Robotics;Notes DaSH continues on half a year after the events of Robotics;Notes. Having spent the previous months studying on the mainland, Kai returns to Tanegashima. On the same ferry rides a certain Super Hacker... DaSH details the adventures of Daru and the returning Robotics;Notes cast. For the most part, the game is a fandisk and does not take itself too seriously. If you wish to skip such service, the reading order for the true route is provided. You can view the document here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Prologue - the Day of the Beginning</title><link href="/2018/12/04/1543965666.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - Prologue - the Day of the Beginning" /><published>2018-12-04T23:21:06+00:00</published><updated>2018-12-04T23:21:06+00:00</updated><id>/2018/12/04/1543965666</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/12/04/1543965666.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - Prologue - the Day of the Beginning
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1543965666.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  This short Drama was released with the original Xbox One opening/ending single CD.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The prologue explores some of the early days of the Newspaper Club, although at moments it turns bittersweet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  My thanks go out to Mouse (&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/5zzb&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@5zzb&lt;/a&gt;) for giving me a Japanese transcript to work from.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Prologue - the Day of the Beginning This short Drama was released with the original Xbox One opening/ending single CD. The prologue explores some of the early days of the Newspaper Club, although at moments it turns bittersweet. My thanks go out to Mouse (@5zzb) for giving me a Japanese transcript to work from. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Far too late - slumbering Fools</title><link href="/2018/11/26/1543268900.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - Far too late - slumbering Fools" /><published>2018-11-26T21:48:20+00:00</published><updated>2018-11-26T21:48:20+00:00</updated><id>/2018/11/26/1543268900</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/11/26/1543268900.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - Far too late - slumbering Fools
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1543268900.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  This is the big one. This Drama CD was part of the Playstation limited edition release.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The main character of this story is Mio. We travel into her past, to investigate the reason as to why she harbours a deep hatred for all Gigalomaniacs.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;strong&gt;
    Major spoilers for the ending of Chaos;Child lie inside, along with minor Steins;Gate spoilers.
  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Far too late - slumbering Fools This is the big one. This Drama CD was part of the Playstation limited edition release. The main character of this story is Mio. We travel into her past, to investigate the reason as to why she harbours a deep hatred for all Gigalomaniacs. Major spoilers for the ending of Chaos;Child lie inside, along with minor Steins;Gate spoilers. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Investigating the mysterious ‘Seven Wonders of Shibuya’</title><link href="/2018/10/27/1540676700.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - Investigating the mysterious 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya'" /><published>2018-10-27T21:45:00+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-27T21:45:00+00:00</updated><id>/2018/10/27/1540676700</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/27/1540676700.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - Investigating the mysterious 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya'
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1540676700.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Time for the second Drama CD from the DVD/BD releases.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  This focuses on Hinae - at the weekend, Hinae 'persuades' Taku to help her investigate the 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya', as research for a story.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - Investigating the mysterious 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya' Time for the second Drama CD from the DVD/BD releases. This focuses on Hinae - at the weekend, Hinae 'persuades' Taku to help her investigate the 'Seven Wonders of Shibuya', as research for a story. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - The Right-sider and a certain day off</title><link href="/2018/10/01/1538423180.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - The Right-sider and a certain day off" /><published>2018-10-01T19:46:20+00:00</published><updated>2018-10-01T19:46:20+00:00</updated><id>/2018/10/01/1538423180</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/10/01/1538423180.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - The Right-sider and a certain day off
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1538423180.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Onto the first of the Drama CDs from the DVD/BD releases.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The story for today focuses on Nono - whilst out shopping with Nono and Yui, Takuru's powerful delusions take hold once more.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Note, I am using the artwork which corresponds to the character featured in the Drama CD, not the artwork that appeared with the Drama CD.
  They wanted main girl on the first release so everything got shifted back one.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - The Right-sider and a certain day off Onto the first of the Drama CDs from the DVD/BD releases. The story for today focuses on Nono - whilst out shopping with Nono and Yui, Takuru's powerful delusions take hold once more. Note, I am using the artwork which corresponds to the character featured in the Drama CD, not the artwork that appeared with the Drama CD. They wanted main girl on the first release so everything got shifted back one. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - The narrow path off the beaten track</title><link href="/2018/09/23/1537729040.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Chaos;Child Drama CD - The narrow path off the beaten track" /><published>2018-09-23T18:57:20+00:00</published><updated>2018-09-23T18:57:20+00:00</updated><id>/2018/09/23/1537729040</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/09/23/1537729040.html">&lt;h3&gt;
  Chaos;Child Drama CD - The narrow path off the beaten track
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  Time to start up translating Chaos;Child content once more. Here for you today is the script of the Comiket 91 Drama CD.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  The story revolves around the Newspaper Club trip to a traditional Japanese inn, complete with onsen. Various activities may or may not occur, depending on the delusion you desire.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  As I have limited video skills; for now it is just a script. I aim to try for one Drama CD each week, starting next on the BD/DVD bonuses.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/12M9VzbTDRwTUFCSp-F47bEg01KmoOMuK2LdisNXVBlI/edit?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;
    You can view the translation here.
  &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  - Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Chaos;Child Drama CD - The narrow path off the beaten track Time to start up translating Chaos;Child content once more. Here for you today is the script of the Comiket 91 Drama CD. The story revolves around the Newspaper Club trip to a traditional Japanese inn, complete with onsen. Various activities may or may not occur, depending on the delusion you desire. As I have limited video skills; for now it is just a script. I aim to try for one Drama CD each week, starting next on the BD/DVD bonuses. You can view the translation here. - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Minikui Mojika no Ko - overview and lyrics</title><link href="/2018/08/16/1534456000.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Minikui Mojika no Ko - overview and lyrics" /><published>2018-08-16T21:46:40+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-16T21:46:40+00:00</updated><id>/2018/08/16/1534456000</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/16/1534456000.html">&lt;h3&gt;
	Minikui Mojika no Ko - overview and lyrics
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	Minikui Mojika no Ko focuses on making you and the characters suffer. It is devoid of any light scenes, the sex scenes are bitter and glimmers of hope are quickly snuffed out.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	A quick overview of the premise. The protagonist, Tanezaki Suteru, is the ugliest person in the world. Having gained a spot in one of the most prestigious schools in the country, he faces daily bullying from the rest of his class. However, he has a special ability/curse; when he gazes at the faces of others, he can read their hearts, with words materialising beside them - Mojika. After another bullied member of his class is forced to falsely confess their love for him, he decides to use his powers to escape and take revenge.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The majority of the game is spent with your gaze directed towards the ground; to objects lying on the floor and the feet of others. The art style focuses on realism and works well with the story themes. Choices are made through deciding when to look up and to use the power of the Mojika. The majority of the main routes are easy to navigate to, but the true route takes a bit more effort (fortunately, there are hints in the stub endings to guide you on your way).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	If you enjoy reading stories which abuse your feelings, make you uncomfortable and have harsh endings, look no further.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe class=&quot;cc&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%; max-height: 50vh; height: 100vh;&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/ms9MTSs438o?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	I have translated the lyrics to the opening and ending songs.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/?post=1534455999&quot;&gt;
		Opening - 憐 (Pitiful)
	&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;/?post=1534455888&quot;&gt;
		Ending - 空 (Sky)
	&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	- Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Minikui Mojika no Ko - overview and lyrics Minikui Mojika no Ko focuses on making you and the characters suffer. It is devoid of any light scenes, the sex scenes are bitter and glimmers of hope are quickly snuffed out. A quick overview of the premise. The protagonist, Tanezaki Suteru, is the ugliest person in the world. Having gained a spot in one of the most prestigious schools in the country, he faces daily bullying from the rest of his class. However, he has a special ability/curse; when he gazes at the faces of others, he can read their hearts, with words materialising beside them - Mojika. After another bullied member of his class is forced to falsely confess their love for him, he decides to use his powers to escape and take revenge. The majority of the game is spent with your gaze directed towards the ground; to objects lying on the floor and the feet of others. The art style focuses on realism and works well with the story themes. Choices are made through deciding when to look up and to use the power of the Mojika. The majority of the main routes are easy to navigate to, but the true route takes a bit more effort (fortunately, there are hints in the stub endings to guide you on your way). If you enjoy reading stories which abuse your feelings, make you uncomfortable and have harsh endings, look no further. I have translated the lyrics to the opening and ending songs. Opening - 憐 (Pitiful) Ending - 空 (Sky) - Minamisawa Senri</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">憐 (Pitiful) lyrics</title><link href="/2018/08/16/1534455999.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="憐 (Pitiful) lyrics" /><published>2018-08-16T21:46:39+00:00</published><updated>2018-08-16T21:46:39+00:00</updated><id>/2018/08/16/1534455999</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2018/08/16/1534455999.html">&lt;h3&gt;
	憐 (Pitiful) lyrics
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img class=&quot;cc mwi&quot; src=&quot;/public/img/1534455999.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	The opening song for Minikui Mojika no Ko. Note: in part, it seems to reference a poem; &quot;Du bist wie eine Blume&quot;. If you were not sure how much suffering is involved in the story, this may help clarify.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Kanji Ver. - 憐&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
ああ　絶望さえ
ああ　甘く響いた
瓦礫さえも　花のようだ
ただ悲しく

ああ　傷跡まで
ああ　甘い想い出
完璧まで　遥か遠く
ただ悲しく

美しい声　聴こえめても
残酷に痛みだけ刺さる
醜い声　視えたとして
ただ悲しく

ああ　壊れる音
ああ　甘い調べ
望んだ時　夢見ている
ただ悲しく

消えない意識　振りほどいて
とりとめに虚しさだけ抱いて
刹那の景色　頬撫でた
ただ悲しく

美しい声　聴こえめても
残酷に痛みだけ刺さる
醜い声　視えたとして
ただ悲しく

可憐
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Romaji Ver. - aware&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
aa, zetsubou sae
aa, amaku hibiita
gareki sae mo, hana no you da
tada kanashiku

aa, kizuato made
aa, amai omoide
kanpeki made haruka tooku
tada kanashiku

utsukushii koe kikoemete mo
zankoku ni itami dake sasaru
minikui koe mieta toshite
tada kanashiku

aa, kowareru oto
aa, amai shirabe
nozonda toki yume miteiru
tada kanashiku

kienai ishiki furi hodoite
toritomeni munashisa dake daite
setsuna no keshiki hoho nadeta
tada kanashiku

utsukushii koe kikoemete mo
zankoku ni itami dake sasaru
minikui koe mieta toshite
tada kanashiku

karen
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;English Ver. - Pitiful&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;l&quot;&gt;
Ah, even the depths of despair
Ah, the sweet reverberations
Even the rubble invokes the same feeling as the flowers
'tis merely sadness

Ah, until scars remain
Ah, the sweet memories
Until perfection is reached; so distant, so far
'tis merely sadness

Even though I can hear your beautiful voice
I am cruelly stricken with suffering
As I can gaze at your ugly voice
'tis merely sadness

Ah, the sounds of breaking
Ah, the sweet observations
The times I longed for can only be seen within my dreams
'tis merely sadness

Relinquish me from this unwavering awareness
Let me embrace only meaningless nothingness
This ephemeral scenery; as you caress my face
'tis merely sadness

Even though I can hear your beautiful voice
I am cruelly stricken with suffering
As I can gaze at your ugly voice
'tis merely sadness

How pitiful
&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
	- Minamisawa Senri
&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">憐 (Pitiful) lyrics The opening song for Minikui Mojika no Ko. Note: in part, it seems to reference a poem; &quot;Du bist wie eine Blume&quot;. If you were not sure how much suffering is involved in the story, this may help clarify. Kanji Ver. - 憐 ああ　絶望さえ ああ　甘く響いた 瓦礫さえも　花のようだ ただ悲しく</summary></entry></feed>